allbestwallpapers.com 2012-06-15

# All Best Wallpapers Privacy Policy

** Allbestwallpapers.com Privacy Policy.**

At Allbestwallpapers.com we take are earnest about protecting your privacy. We have compiled this privacy policy so that you can understand how we take your privacy in consideration and how we deal with any personal information that you may provide us with. 

** Advertising via Third Parties.   **

We have third party advertising companies showcasing their adverts on our site.   This helps us to earn an income and to be able to provide you with a free service.  Please take note that should you click on any of their links that you are no longer under the protection of our privacy policy.  Before you offer any of your detail we recommend that you carefully read their respective privacy policies.  While some of the advertisers on our site may collect cookies, we do not receive any of the information that they obtain from you.

** Selling or sharing or your Data**

At Allbestwallpapers.com we have a policy of not selling or sharing any of your private details.

** Third Party Cookies**

What is a cookie?

         A cookie is a bit of data that a website uses to save your what you like. 

While Allbestwallpapers.com does not collect cookies, many of the advertisers that use our site may use cookies.  Kindly check their respective privacy policies before giving permission.

** Sharing of your personal information**

Kindly note that the only information we share with our advertisers and sponsors is statistical for them to calculate the impact of an advertisement, banner or logo.

At times we log your IP addresses and we wish you to understand that this is for the sole purpose of systems admin or for average statistics to our advertisers. 

We do not disclose any of your personal information unless legally bound to do so.  We are bound by law to disclose personal information should a court order be obtained for such purposes.

**Minors**

Minors under the age of 12 may not provide us with any of their personal information and we advise that they should never access the internet without adult supervision.

**Promotional/Marketing Material**

Note that you are not under any obligation to accept promotional or marketing information from Allbestwallpapers.com and advertisers on our site.  Any offers will always come with an option not to receive this material.  Any mailings that you agree to receive will in additional always provide you with the option to unsubscribe.

**Questions**

If there is anything in our privacy policy that you require clarification on please feel free to contact us on:  [ info@allbestwallpapers.com](mailto:info@allbestwallpapers.com).

**Spam**

Allbestwallpapers.com undertakes not to partake in any spamming activity.  Any mailing sent to you will be only as a result of your specific request.

**Ownership**

Allbestwallpapers would like members to understand that we do not own any wallpapers as they are added by members.  They are subject to the copyright cover of their respective owners that submitted them to our site.  If at anybody that owns a wallpaper requests that their wallpaper be removed it can be done.  Allbestwallpapers does not sell, rent or buy any of the wallpaper this is a completely free service.

**Permission**

By navigating our website Allbestwallpapers.com you hereby provide your agreement to the Privacy policy of our site.  Should you not approve of any of the terms within our Privacy Policy you are welcome to contact us with your concerns but do not that you should not continue to utilize our site (as stated prior to this, navigation of our site indicates acceptance of our policies).   At any time we reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy.
